<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>project on</title><link>https://brain.lipowczan.pl/tags/project/</link><description>Recent content in project on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://brain.lipowczan.pl/tags/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cosmos</title><link>https://brain.lipowczan.pl/CRYPTOS/ANALYSIS/Cosmos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brain.lipowczan.pl/CRYPTOS/ANALYSIS/Cosmos/</guid><description>#todo
Cosmos Find information: Cryptocurrency Prices, Charts And Market Capitalizations | CoinMarketCap
Actual market cap Circulating supply Max Supply Current ranking in terms of market capitalization Presence on exchanges (liquidity and number of exchanges) Specify: The usefulness of the project (whether it solves a specific problem and whether it is possible) Current stage of development (check the roadmap) Experience and skills of the team (check LinkedIn profiles of team members) Planned events ( https://coinmarketcal.</description></item><item><title>Filecoin</title><link>https://brain.lipowczan.pl/CRYPTOS/ANALYSIS/Filecoin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brain.lipowczan.pl/CRYPTOS/ANALYSIS/Filecoin/</guid><description>#todo
Filecoin Find information: Cryptocurrency Prices, Charts And Market Capitalizations | CoinMarketCap
Actual market cap Circulating supply Max Supply Current ranking in terms of market capitalization Presence on exchanges (liquidity and number of exchanges) Specify: The usefulness of the project (whether it solves a specific problem and whether it is possible) It solved the problem with storing files on the blockchain in decentralized way.</description></item><item><title>Polygon</title><link>https://brain.lipowczan.pl/CRYPTOS/ANALYSIS/Polygon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brain.lipowczan.pl/CRYPTOS/ANALYSIS/Polygon/</guid><description>Polygon Find information: Cryptocurrency Prices, Charts And Market Capitalizations | CoinMarketCap Cryptocurrency Prices, Charts, and Crypto Market Cap | CoinGecko</description></item></channel></rss>